[Those who believe in the supremacy of money]
[will eventually become hungry wolves.]
[When they greedily tear apart their own kind,]
[they forget that they were once humans who walked on two legs.]
[The brighter the glory of a wealthy family,]
[the deeper the shadow on the other side.]
[The rose you crowned me with]
[has long withered into a thorn.]
[I planted thorns in the ruins]
[where you burned me to ashes.]
[The trending topic is blowing up.]
[The rich family's son-in-law cheated on his brother's fiancée.]
[Even TV dramas wouldn't dare to film this plot.]
[The Golden Silk Group's]
[Dark Fairy Tale series fashion show is approaching.]
[But the controlling family, the Lu family,]
[has just revealed such a shocking scandal.]
[Aren't the Lu couple very much in love?]
[How did their image collapse so suddenly?]
[He must have fallen for someone else.]
[And it's his brother's fiancée.]
[Cheaters, just get a divorce!]
[Tonight,]
[they will climb your sturdy castle,]
[and carve your sins]
[on every stone brick.]
Shen Jingmo,
why are you here?
I knew you would choose to face everything.
Put it on.
At least it will protect you
from those hurtful words.
Focus on your live broadcast.
I'll handle the rest.
The trending topic you see
is stirring up a storm that threatens to engulf me.
Look,
that mistress from the news is going live!
And at the eye of this storm, the woman dubbed despicable
stands right before you.
That's right,
I'm the woman in the news.
Now, I want to share with you
everything I've been through and the truth.
Where should I start?
Let's start from the time I met him in France.
14 to 13.
14 to 14.
The final sword.
Ah.
Be careful.
Are you okay?
15 to 14.
You lost.
Have some water.
How did you find this fencing club?
And how do you know I've never lost here?
I'm here on a business trip.
I heard that
there's a very skilled female fencer here.
I lost convincingly today.
Fencing is an art,
not just a sport.
But it's also a happy thing
to meet you.
What's your name?
Your left hand.
This is my name.
It depends on whether you can guess it.
Jiang Li.
Do you have time in the evening?
I'll treat you to a meal.
Just a meal?
Just a meal.
Staying in a huge villa for just two days.
you rich folks really live it up.
Provençal blood (wine).
Did you specifically ask the hotel to prepare this?
A ring mark on the ring finger.
Are you married?
Do you care?
Ma'am,
this is the place.
Someone's coming in.
I'll go check.
Honey.
Why are you in France?
The wine of Provence.
The hotel gave it to us.
I accidentally
spilled it.
I haven't cleaned it up yet.
Hmm.
Honey.
Yes?
What a pretty bracelet.
I saw it at the mall.
I thought
it suits you well.
Thank you, honey.
Guess
why I came to France.
Yeah.
Why didn't you
tell me in advance?
I'm here
to discuss with my mom
about holding a proper wedding ceremony.
We've been
married for so long,
and Mumu is already five years old.
Chairman,
will she agree?
My mom agreed.
Although
she just had surgery,
and is recuperating in France.
She can't attend the ceremony.
But she said
during this period,
you will be the temporary head of Golden Silks.
Really?
Yes.
Are you happy?
I finally got my mom's approval.
Alright.
I'll go change into my pajamas.
Honey.
That's great.
I really love you so much.
Honey.
But you're holding me too tightly.
I can hardly breathe.
Guess who called?
Zhou Jian.
I know you're watching the live broadcast.
[Why did you call me from an unfamiliar number?]
[Are you feeling guilty?]
[Or are you afraid?]
[You thought you could control the game of fate.]
[How ridiculous.]
[I'm the one who truly controls everything.]
Where were we?
Oh, I remember now.
Jiang Li.
We met again a month later,
at the new collection launch of Golden Silks.
[I know many people]
[would call me a mistress,]
[and judge me as a heartless woman.]
[But I'm a human being.]
[Who cares about the truth?]
[I didn't do it for money,]
[or for fun.]
[I knew very well]
[he had a family,]
[a wife,]
[and a child.]
So you must be curious why I did this, right?
Now let me reveal the answer.
I want them
all
to die.